<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team Members on Pragati 2K22</title>
    <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team Members on Pragati 2K22</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/amal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/amal/</guid>
      <description>Amal Wilson Varghese hails from Wayanad, Kerala. He majored in Molecular biology from University of Mysore and is currently pursuing PhD at Division of molecular medicine, SCTIMST. He is driven by his passion towards biology and looks for ways to improve the existence of an organism. His area of interest includes molecular biology, neurobiology, and therapeutics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/arun_mitra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/arun_mitra/</guid>
      <description>Arun Mitra is a PhD Scholar at Achutha Menon Centre for Health Science Studies, Sree Chitra Tirunal Institute for Medical Sciences and Technology, Trivandrum. He has a background in Public Health with an MD in Community Medicine from Maharashtra University of Health Sciences, Nashik. His current area of research is focused on health data science with domain expertise in public health. He is currently looking at how data science can contribute to transforming routine health data into evidence for public health decision-making as part of his research work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/arun_vs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/arun_vs/</guid>
      <description>Arun V S, is a student of Diploma in Operation Theatre and Anesthesia Technology at SCTIMST. He has completed his diploma in Electronics Engineering in 2020. He is a native of Trivandrum and indulges in sports like football and cricket. He is an enthusiastic information seeker and strongly believes in energy, passion and dedication towards his work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ashis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ashis/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Ashis, a medical doctor who graduated from Trivandrum Medical college, has a post-graduation in Community Medicine from KEM, Mumbai. After a one-year stint in ICMR-Delhi as medical scientist, he joined Achutha menon center as a Research Officer in the institute&amp;rsquo;s HTA unit.
While he is pursuing a Doctorate in health economics, he is also keen on health policy and equity in medicine. He was a fellow in the IHSC-NITI Aayog Mentor-Mentee Program and has won accolades in national level poster presentation and essay writing competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/aswathy_bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/aswathy_bi/</guid>
      <description>Born and brought up in Trivandrum, Kerala. She graduated MBBS from KUHS university in 2017 and has worked under renowned doctors of surgical gastroenterology, KIMS, Trivandrum. She nurtures a passion in public health and is currently pursuing Masters in Public Health in AMCHSS, SCTIMST.
She is an accomplished athlete having achievements in sports such as Kho Kho, Badminton and Tracks. She loves upcycled crafting, gardening and is an adept cook. Loves pushing beyond her limits, conquering new challenges, and looking forward to a brighter future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/athira_kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/athira_kr/</guid>
      <description>Athira K R is currently pursuing her PhD in the Division of thrombosis Research unit SCTIMST. She has many feathers in her cap including: BSc. Chemistry from Union Christian College, Aluva, MSc. Biopolymer Science from CIPET, Kochi and an MPhil. Biomedical Technology – SCTIMST, Trivandrum.
She has been an active NCC Cadet and has had an enriching experience through her various stints which have equipped her with wide knowledge and many skills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/athira_m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/athira_m/</guid>
      <description>Athira M. is a post graduate in Chemistry and pursuing her Ph.D.in 3D Printing of Polymeric Biomaterials in the Division of Polymeric Medical Devices, BMT Wing, SCTIMST. She enjoys dancing and loves to belt out tunes through her singing and lovely voice. She has a zeal for reading and believes in enjoying the simple things in life</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/chunoti_punwatkar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/chunoti_punwatkar/</guid>
      <description>Ayurveda graduate from Maharashtra, currently MPH batch 2022 student.
An avid listener of her friends, loves capturing moments through her photography. She believes in always trying to make a difference in her own small ways, happily backpacking through different states as well as life itself!
Has a love for music, handicrafts and can put her own twist to conjuring up amazing stuff- always willing to learn more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/deepanjan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/deepanjan/</guid>
      <description>A traveller and foodie by passion and a doctor by profession, Dr Deepanjan joined DM Cardiology at SCTIMST in January 2020 after completing his MD at PGIMER Chandigarh.
Although he is known for his brilliant academic track record with numerous awards and Gold Medals, along with over 100 publications and presentations, very few are aware of his multiple hobbies including swimming, cooking, art and music, and his awards of Mr Rhapsody in 2010 (MCK) and Mr Zenith in 2019 (PGIMER)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/george_joseph_kodickal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/george_joseph_kodickal/</guid>
      <description>Dr George, a MBBS graduate currently pursuing Masters in Public Health at AMCHSS. He is an avid quizzer, a passionate history buff who loves to indulge in nonfiction literature and loves travelling to locations where history sleeps. He is a footballer and keenly follows EPL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/gokul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/gokul/</guid>
      <description>Dr Gokul G Pillai an MBBS graduate and a public health aspirant currently pursuing Mater of Public Health in Achutha Menon Centre for Health Science Studies – SCTIMST Trivandrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ishika_arora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ishika_arora/</guid>
      <description>A dentist by profession, Punjabi kudi at heart. Currently pursuing her Masters in Public health at SCTIMST. Likes to Dabbles with firing up other&amp;rsquo;s tastebuds with her cooking and is a hardcore connoisseur. Loves all things - &amp;ldquo;fashion&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;fitness&amp;rdquo; and has a must-hear collection of music in her Spotify!
“To summarize my magnanimous life in a sentence would just be pure embarrassment”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/jishnu_pawan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/jishnu_pawan/</guid>
      <description>K. Jishnu Pawan, is a Researcher, currently pursuing Doctoral Degree in Health Sciences at SCTIMST, has completed his undergraduate in BSc (Nursing), a Postgraduate in Social Work and is a Doctoral Student of Philosophy in Public Health.
This background has equipped him with enhanced knowledge in the area of empowerment and resilience thinking. His skills have allowed him to dabble between various roles: as an educator, an entrepreneur, a counselor, a manager and a public speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/kajal_prajapati/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/kajal_prajapati/</guid>
      <description>An Occupational therapist with lots of charm and fun on her mind. She believes in empathy and reaching out to the needy, having worked with autistic kids and those suffering from cerebral palsy, it reignited her passion for community work and public health. That brought her to pursuing MPH at SCTIMST.
A constant caring friend with a penchant for classical dance and embodying skills in dance form: Kathak. She is amazing with a badminton racquet, Bball and great at teaching her friends before exams!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/markose_paret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/markose_paret/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Markose L Paret is a Senior Resident in DM Cardiac Anaesthesiology program. He is currently on study leave from Armed Forces Medical Services. He really enjoys football, loves to tune in to different genres of music and can get lost in non-fiction books hoping to widen his horizons.
&amp;ldquo;Hope to catch you all at SCAAF PRAGATI 2022&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/medha_surendranath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/medha_surendranath/</guid>
      <description>Medha Surendranath is a PhD student at Biomedical Technology Wing of SCTIMST. She is a post graduate in chemistry, currently doing research in the development of polymeric materials for biomedical applications. Loves to dance and has great oration skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/mehrunnisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/mehrunnisa/</guid>
      <description>Dr Mehrunnisa, a Dental graduate currently pursuing Masters in Public Health at AMCHHS, SCTIMST. Self-certified bookworm. Aspiring poet and author. Die hard BTS fan/ARMY On a mission to befriend every kindred soul with the same love for the band. An absolute sucker for all things cute and furry. Prefers if life slowed down and allowed us to marvel at the beauty of simple things.
&amp;ldquo;Let’s meet at Pragati 2022!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/sanjay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/sanjay/</guid>
      <description>A Trivian who graduated in BSc. Nursing from KUHS university in 2019. Currently pursuing diploma in CVT nursing in SCTIMST. He is a freelance photographer and videographer who is peculiar in capturing nature and urban styles. A voyager who loves to travel a lot and an automobile enthusiast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/sarah_lukhose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/sarah_lukhose/</guid>
      <description>Sarah Lukhose is pursuing Ph.D. in the Department of Medical Devices Engineering, Biomedical Technology Wing, SCTIMST, and a recipient of the University Grants Commission&amp;rsquo;s Senior Research Fellowship. She is currently involved in researching several polymeric composite biomaterials that can be used for biomedical applications. She has completed her master&amp;rsquo;s and bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Biochemistry from SB College, Changanassery, under Mahatma Gandhi University, and from SNGC, Coimbatore, under Bharathiar University, respectively. She loves to explore the beauty of nature and enjoys capturing them through her vivid photography</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/shivanand_kumatagi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/shivanand_kumatagi/</guid>
      <description>Dr Shivanand Kumatagi from Department of Transfusion Medicine. He is a certified MBBS doctor currently pursuing his MD. He is an avid football and hockey player who also follows cricket closely. He is an Instagram lover. Enjoys participating in co-curricular and extracurricular activities.
“Let&amp;rsquo;s all take a bit of our busy schedule and entertain ourselves in this extravaganza fest.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ss_lal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/ss_lal/</guid>
      <description>Dr. S.S Lal (Sadasivan Sreemathy Lal) is a leading intellectual from India who has played a seminal role in transforming Public Health internationally. Starting from a humble background, Dr. Lal has shown the way of how any dedicated individual could rise to the international stage and make huge impacts on social service delivery.
His focus was on ensuring the highest quality care delivery in a very limited resource setting. During his stint in East Timor, and later through program implementation in Ethiopia, Zambia, Vietnam, and Bangladesh, he applied his hands-on learning to get things done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/tijo_george/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/tijo_george/</guid>
      <description>A dentist turned public health professional. Dr George worked with National and International agencies before joining for PhD in Achutha Menon Centre for Health Science Studies, SCTIMST. His PhD broadly focuses on migration and health. He enjoys sports, loves to travel and has a keen interest in Data visualization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/veena_cs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sandbox-devfesttoulouse.firebaseapp.com/speakers/veena_cs/</guid>
      <description>A student, pursuing PG Diploma in Neurotechnology at SCTIMST. She has done her under graduation in BSc. Chemistry from Mother Theresa college Nellikad. Believes in leading a simple life and is active on social media. She is a passionate dancer who has enthralled audiences through different stage performances including Kalothsavam.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
